biblicalarchaeology.org 2006-08-25

# Biblical Archaeology Society

Biblical Archaeology Society Privacy Statement

**Information about our organization and Web site**

The Biblical Archaeology Society was founded in 1974 as a nonprofit, nondenominational, educational organization dedicated to the dissemination of information about archaeology in the Bible lands. BAS educates the public about archaeology and the Bible through magazines, books, visual materials and seminars.

This privacy policy covers the Biblical Archaeology Society and its Web site.

Organization Name and Address:

> Biblical Archaeology Society  
>  4710 41st St. NW  
>  Washington, DC 20016  
>  US

Controllers:

> Biblical Archaeology Society  
>  CDS Fulfillment

Web Site:

> http://www.bib-arch.org/

Alternate URLs (all point to same Web site):

> http://www.archaeologyodyssey.org/  
>  http://www.biblereview.org/  
>  http://www.biblicalarchaeology.org/  
>  http://www.biblicalarchaeologyreview.org/  
>  http://www.biblicalarchaeololysociety.org/

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

**The services and links of our Web site**   

Our Web site enables you to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect only your email address and a name of your choosing. 

Our Web site does not include links to third party Web service providers.

**Automatic Collection of Information**

We do not use cookies on our Web site. 

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**   

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. 

To access the tables of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please  click here . 

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. 

We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us. 

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data. 

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations. 

**Confidentiality / Security**

We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data: 

  * primary personal data (such as name and contact details) 

  * identifiers (such as credit card details, Web site password) 

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorized access 

  * improper use or disclosure 

  * unauthorized modification 

  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss 

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

**Access to the personal data we may hold about you**

You can ask us whether we are keeping personal data about you, and/or reqest a copy of your personal data, by using any of the methods below: 

  * sending an email ([webmaster@bib-arch.org](mailto:webmaster@bib-arch.org?SUBJECT=Personal%20Information%20Request))

  * sending a request by mail to: 

> Biblical Archaeology Society  
>  Personal Information Request  
>  4710 41st St. NW  
>  Washington, DC 20016 

  * calling us at 202-364-3300

We will provide you within a month with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you. although we may require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge. 

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 

  * erased 

  * rectified or amended 

  * completed 

We currently do not reserve the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

**Privacy Compliance**  

To the best of our knowledge, there are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. 

To the best of our knowledge, there are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization.

* * *

Primary personal data/Business information 

An x [ **x** ] indicates that personal data is collected of the type shown and for the reason shown. 

A dash [ - ] indicates that no personal data of the type shown is collected for the reason shown. 

In no case do we collect personal data that is not volunteered by the visitor.   

|  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Name  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

**x**

| 

**x**

| 

\-   
  
Gender  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Address  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

**x**

| 

**x**

| 

\-   
  
E-mail address  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

**x**

| 

**x**

| 

\-   
  
Phone/Fax number  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

**x**

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
other (describe)    
| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
|  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Employer/organization  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Job title  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Address  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
E-mail address  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Phone/Fax number  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
other (describe)    
| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Other personal details and profiling data 

An x [ **x** ] indicates that personal data is collected of the type shown and for the reason shown. 

A dash [ \- ] indicates that no personal data of the type shown is collected for the reason shown. 

In no case do we collect personal data that is not volunteered by the visitor.   

|  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Personal details  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Physical description  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Family characteristics  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Education and skills  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Life style or personal tastes  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Financial resources  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
other (describe)    
| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Identifiers 

An x [ **x** ] indicates that personal data is collected of the type shown and for the reason shown. 

A dash [ - ] indicates that no personal data of the type shown is collected for the reason shown. 

In no case do we collect personal data that is not volunteered by the visitor.  

|  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
On-line identifiers  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Financial identifiers  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

**x**

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
identifiers assigned by Public bodies  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Biometrics identifiers  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
other (describe)    
| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Specific Data 

An x [ **x** ] indicates that personal data is collected of the type shown and for the reason shown. 

A dash [ - ] indicates that no personal data of the type shown is collected for the reason shown. 

In no case do we collect personal data that is not volunteered by the visitor.  

  |  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Racial or ethnic origin  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Political opinions  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Religious or philosophical beliefs  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Trade union membership  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Health/Medical data  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Sex life  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Police/Justice data such as civil/criminal actions brought by or against the visitor  | 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
other (describe)    
| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-
